designposts.net 2017-12-25

# Privacy

With the internet advancing, reaching more horizons, it is evident that the data available on the internet becomes more crucial. Privacy is a major concern in these times. Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us, and we ensure absolute measures in order to protect it. To protect your privacy, read on to find out more about that information that we may gather upon your visit to this website. You will also learn how the information is used (if it is).

**Google AdSense**

The website employs the use of Google AdSense in order to display advertisements from different vendors. Having said that, the DoubleClick DART cookie is used to serve advertisements on this website.

  * **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google uses these cookies in order to target their advertisements. The advertisements displayed on this website will be based on your search history, and the websites you have visited in the past. If you are willing to opt out of these cookies, you may visit the Google **ad and content network** [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Google is responsible for tracking of users through the use of DART cookies. Please rest assured the this website has no control of the information that is patched through to Google and neither is the information accessible.

**Personal Information**

When you visit this website, your current IP address will be logged down. That will be accompanied by the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to access trends, track user movements and prevent anything illegal. Furthermore, please rest assured that the IP address are not linked to any information that can be sued to identify a person.

**Third-Party Websites**

While you are browsing this website, you will come across various different links which we use for legal reasons and for reference. While we maintain that the links are safe, we are not responsible for the privacy policy on those websites. Please be aware that privacy policies differ on every website.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy may be changed at any time. If you have questions regarding the privacy policy or any changes that you may have noticed please contact us at the following e-mail. We will be happy to answer your questions and concerns.

**[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)designposts.net**
